//Creating an array and passing the number, question , option and answer;

let questions = [
     {
    numb:1,
    question: " Wrapping data and its related functionality into a single entity is known as _____________",
    answer: "Encapsulation",
    options :[
        "Abstraction",
        "Encapsulation",
        "Polymorphism",
        "Modularity"
    ]
},
{   numb:2,
    question: "What does polymorphism in OOPs mean?",
    answer: "allowing overiding of functions",
    options :[
        "hiding data",
        "allowing overiding of functions",
        "keeping things in differnt modules/files",
        "wrapping things into a single unit"
    ]
    
},
{   numb:3,
    question: "How access specifiers in Class helps in Abstraction?",
    answer: "They allows us to show only required things to outer world",
    options :[
        "They does not helps in any way",
        "They allows us to show only required things to outer world",
        "They help in keeping things together",
        "Abstraction concept is not used in classes"
    ]
},
{   numb:4,
    question: "Which of the following is correct?",
    answer: "Derived class pointer object cannot point to a base class object",
    options :[
        "Base class pointer object cannot point to a derived class object",
        "Derived class pointer object cannot point to a base class object",
        "A derived class cannot have pointer objects",
        "A base class cannot have pointer objects"
    ]
},
{   numb:5,
    question: "Out of the following, which is not a member of the class?",
    answer: "Friend function",
    options :[
        "Friend function",
        "Constant function",
        "Virtual function",
        "Static function"
    ]
},
{   numb:6,
    question: " Which of these best describes an array?",
    answer: "Container of objects of similar types",
    options :[
        "A data structure that shows a hierarchical behaviour",
        "Container of objects of similar types",
        "Arrays are immutable once initialised",
        "Array is not a data structure"
    ]
},
{   numb:7,
    question: "When does the ArrayIndexOutOfBoundsException occur?",
    answer: "Run-time",
    options :[
        "Compile-time",
        "Run-time",
        "Not an error",
        "Not an exception at all"
    ]
},

{   numb:8,
    question: "Assuming int is of 4bytes, what is the size of int arr[15];?",
    answer: "60",
    options :[
        "15",
        "20",
        "30",
        "60"
    ]
  
},
{   numb:9,
    question: "What is the time complexity to count the number of elements in the linked list",
    answer: "O(n)",
    options :[
        "O(1)",
        "O(logn)",
        "O(n)",
        "O(n2)"
    ]
},
{   numb:10,
    question: "What is the average case time complexity of insertion sort?",
    answer: "O(n2)",
    options :[
        "O(n)",
        "O(nlogn)",
        "O(n2)",
        "O(logn)"
    ]
},
];

